Check it out ibile fleshstick!
Come on!
Don't be silly, put them on each other and laugh.
Put it on.
bitch
Bebo alright
Laboratory
Oka Dance
Buchimatteirimashita
Some of your oj
universe
division of name
bevor specifications
bevor mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora mora
Wah!
Wow!
Oh no!
I don't know anything!
All I can understand is Otani!
The whole of Japan rejoiced at the WBC!
Samurai Japan's new album B9 was released on the day of their victory.
New album B9
Super Express took on the challenge of its release event.
I wanted the four new members to produce the event.
It was the first time for the new members to produce an event
The ideas we're all coming up with are pretty high-level.
So it would be cool if we could do it at the front or in a box where we could make a big decision.
That would be cool.
It's tough. It's tough, isn't it?
Well, our feelings...
I've told them exactly how we feel.
I'm sure we'll go on from there.
I'm sure.
I wonder...
I think we're both aiming in the same direction.
I think we're on the same page.
I think so.
I'm rather looking forward to it.
I wonder how it's going to be.
I wonder what it will be like.
Who will do it?
It's like this with the teacher.
After that
The new members had many discussions
The set list was decided
But the way they would appear, their costumes...
and what kind of things to talk about at that mc were decided.
This year, we have a goal of Gouland Stylish.
This year, we have a goal, or rather a purpose
I'm not going to shift my focus
I'm not going to shift my axis.
I've chosen cool songs for all of them.
I'm thinking of going with a super express style that shows
Please read from "Connections".
Please read from the connection.
At the final rehearsal, everyone checks the beginning of the songs in detail.
Does New World have a lot of songs?
Yes, that's how it started. I'm already sitting down from the beginning.
I would like to have them tell me New World.
Wouldn't it be better to have them confirm when they sit down and say New World?
On the contrary.
Which definitely doesn't fit. If I say "New World," it will be very different.
So either way is fine.
Let's all stand up.
Let's all stand up, and let's play "New World" by Mr. Takahashi.
Do you want to join hands then?
If you want to join hands, let's do it like this.
Let's see how you do it.
That's it.
I can't help but think back to the way we used to do it.
I remember how we used to do it.
I tend to rub them together.
But this time, we decided to entrust the work to a double-digit number of members.
We've decided to leave it to the double-digit members this time, so we can't look at our fixed ideas
I was also thinking that I should not be able to look at it in a good way.
I was also thinking about it as I watched the performance.
And for the first time at this event, B9's lead track "Mora" was performed.
B9's lead track "Moramora Mora
I heard that it has a simple high note.
Let's count the chorus one more time
Just in case the angle and so on...You know, the angles and stuff.
That's why we managed to get the angles right.
In order to perform the dance perfectly matched to the live performance
We rehearsed very carefully to make sure our dances would be perfectly matched for the live performance.
I really want to practice this part.
Practice already?
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
I don't want to stiff them here.
I don't think we're ever going to get it here.
From the side, from an angle, it's just off.
It's not too bad.
And maybe he's too far down.
Right hand.
Yeah, yeah, I guess.
In a way, it's better than doing it in a proper box, because you can't show it with a high degree of perfection unless you stick to it tightly and everyone sticks to it with a high level of awareness.
At the same time, it's also the release date of the album.
It's only five songs, but they are five songs.
I want everyone to suddenly put their souls into those five songs, and to get off to a good start.
I would like to make the live concert a success.
That's all for now. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Final rehearsal is over.
Yes, sir.
Go, go, go, go, go!
And then...
I wonder if this is going to be videotaped...
by everyone
I'll get it.
Let's do it again, shall we?
Sure.
That's...
I'm gonna jump ahead.
I'll jump.
Time.
Crackle, crackle, crackle
Oh, wow
Sing, sing, sing, sing, sing
Wow! Sorry!
Whoo!
♪ Singing, singing, singing, singing ♪
Oh, I must have made a mistake! Sorry.
♪ Singing, singing, singing
Kin!
Yes, Bing.
One at a time.
One, huh? One at a time.
I'll start with you.
One at a time.
That's okay.
That's good. That's good.
Kin.
from the end
From the end
Thank you very much.
Sing, sing, sing, sing
Thank you for your hard work!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Yeah!
Cheer for the game, please.
Hope you.
Hope you
Let's go
Bet's Piping
Hi, hi, hi
Kaai
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
yee-ha ha ha ha ha
Yee-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ya-ya-ya-ya.
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Yee-haw. Yee-haw.
Yay-ay-ay-ay.
Yee-ha ha!
Yay.Yay!
Yay.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo.
I knew this was gonna happen.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going...
Yes, yes...
Okay, okay.
Yes!
Yay!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Perfect.
Thank you for all your hard work.
I'll do it one last time... one last time.
Applause.
BGM
Eleven RIders
Music for Lions
Thank you for watching!
Onward I go
Ride on Up, up, up Get down If you're ready to give up
If you're that ready Good bye
Ride on Up, up, up, up I can't go back tomorrow
My dream that will carry us through our lives
Baby I wanna be a superstar
So crazy to start
Good bye
Baby I wanna be a superstar
We don't stop calling
Start throwing it all at me My dream
Thank you
Next song
Um, just one song.
Ladies and gentlemen...
You can film.
Okay.
Just one song.
But I want to shoot a video here.
I'll take it, I'll take it, I'll take it!
One of the production ideas by Weekya
MoroMoroMoro
first performance!
Today's performance was the lead song of B9
Mora Mora
Viva la mora mora mora oka dance
That morning, if all of a sudden our hands were joined
Slowly approaching, soaring youth
Chirara, if you ran
I want my heart to beat faster People who can't dance are waiting in a daze
Dostrike in the midst of the onslaught
In fact, it's a little action
Chirichiritiri bosom tingles Let me know
Kurokunta kudasareta koko Ready for you
Mikura no toko ni one-one make class
Kira make-up with echoyaki
Matching Hotel Time
VIVA Ranmoramora Oka Dance
VIVA Ai no Horn Ka Weak
VIVA Ranmola Mora Oka Dance
VIVA Jenny Kubiru no na
Tata tansa, tata tansa, tata tansa
Burn it on.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Hi hara hara, today's la off viva
Viva!
Rumoran mora oka dance viva
Ran moran mora oka dance viva
Come on, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it, throw it.
Rummoranmola Oka DanceRammorangmola Oka Dance
Burn it into your groove.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Let's go for the last spurt!
Hey everyone! It's time for this dance together!
What if you've been waiting around the corner?
Ready, set, go!
Even if someone doesn't know the song later, we can still make it a big hit.
You can sing it in your adult voice
Let's all have fun and dance!
Everybody dance, everybody dance, everybody dance
Repeat you I'll pull my eyes out and dance
I'll go over the limits that I've shaken off and I'll go over them again
I'll be strong
Because I don't want to give up
The courage to stand up to the odds is the bond that binds us together
I'll never be afraid to be present
And so the Twiste concert was a great success
And then...
Yes, I know it's a little embarrassing, but here we go
And we're on our way!
Yes!
Super Express's legendary benefit event
Train Gokko is back for one night only!
New members will experience the legendary event for the first time!
Warm interaction and support with fans only possible at a release event!
That's all, we are Super Express! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
It's been a long time since we had the opportunity to do this event.
Of course I felt nostalgic at first, but
but it was replaced by a fresh feeling.
Above all, it was not only us.
I was really happy that not only us, but also everyone in Car 8 enjoyed the show.
I was really happy that not only us but also the people in car No. 8 enjoyed the show.
It was like a reissue of the original.
I really felt that way.
I want to cherish such things in the future.
It was nostalgic and fun.
We had a lot of fun.
We had a lot of fun, and I'm glad we were able to do that.
I think the most important thing is how everyone who came enjoyed themselves.
I think that's the most important thing.
I wonder how many people saw the show by chance.
I hope that something stuck with those people.
I am very grateful that we have been able to do this for more than 10 years.
I am very thankful that we have been able to do this for more than 10 years.
Ten years have passed, and we have become nine members.
I felt it was very meaningful that the album was released on the same day.
I had a lot of fun.
Above all, I felt it was very worthwhile.
I was very happy to see that
The four members of Nigita Gousha thought about everything from the setlist to the details of the live performance.
They thought of everything down to the smallest detail.
I was very happy because I could reconfirm their feelings for Super Express.
I was so happy to be able to reconfirm their feelings for Chotokkyu.
Yuki, who had been watching over the new members' live performance, said
I thought that it was very modern to make a live concert with the involvement of SNS.
I thought it was very important.
I thought it was a B live show that gave us new discoveries.
We were very good at approaching the outside world.
I thought it was important for them to be involved in SNS nowadays.
I'm looking forward to seeing their unique performances in the future.
I'm really looking forward to seeing more of them in the future.
How about the new members after the first produced live performance?
There were things we could have done better, and there were also things we could have done better.
If I have the chance to do another free live performance in the future, I would like to make the most of what I have learned this time and make the best of it.
I would like to make use of what I learned this time and change the composition and direction.
For the time being, this time was a success.
I was able to realize once again that it is not a matter of course that people will come to a free live show.
The audience cheered from the moment we appeared on stage.
There were so many people from Hachioji who shouted just when their eyes met mine.
I thought it would be better to go through the center of the stage and make them feel loud, so I did that.
I thought it was the right thing to do.
When Kai-kun was at the rehearsal and I performed the song "Moramora", he said, "Please listen to this song.
I told him to listen to it, but he didn't ask me to listen to it at all.
He told me that he doesn't ask me to listen to it very often.
He told me that he doesn't really ask me to listen to it.
I realized once again that you are very thorough about that.
I'm still thinking about that.
I guess it's because we've been doing it for half a year and we've been doing it for 10 years.
I realized that there are still a lot of things that we don't know about them because we've only been doing it for six months.I thought that there are many things that we don't yet know about that are only possible because it's so clear.
I hope to be able to direct with this knowledge in the future.
I think the artists are cool.
I think that Shuya and Masahiro are the ones who know what they're doing.
I think Shuya and Masahiro are the ones who know what they're doing.
I knew these two would be great.
There were a few things we had prepared that ended up being rejected.
but I'm sure they were great.
If there is another opportunity like this
I would love to do it again.
It ended well, didn't it?
I had a great sense of accomplishment.
The response was great.
We thought about it this way, and we did it this way.
If the recipient didn't think anything of it, it would be meaningless.
If the recipient has a good reaction like that...
We are very happy when the recipient has a good reaction or a good expression.
I'm very happy and I'm glad that we did it.
I'm glad we were able to do it.
Thank you very much.
It's been 5 or 6 years since I've seen Hatsune, so I'm really happy.
It's great to be able to see everyone in person.
I thought it was normal to be able to hear your voices, but that's been overturned since then.
I realized how happy it makes me to hear your voice like this.
I've been immersed in it for a long time.
I only took one picture, but I hope it will become a precious memory of this day.
I was able to confirm that the four new members had their own opinions about the production.
If there are any, I would like to make the most of them.
We'll be going around a lot, so I hope we can all go around without hesitation.
I'll be with you all the way.
I'll be with you all the way, all the way, My life.